Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- [24-inch Clark Refractor], 1909; phaedra0674 (Box 23)
  KG11365.673
  7
- [24-inch Clark Refractor], 1909/1910; phaedra0675 (Box 23)
  KG11365.674
  8
- [24-inch Clark Refractor], 1910/1911; phaedra0676 (Box 23)
  KG11365.675
  9
- Photometric Observations, 1872; phaedra0677 (Box 23)
  KG11365.676
- Photometric Observations, 1872; phaedra0678 (Box 23)
  KG11365.677
  2
- Photometric Observations, 1872; phaedra0679 (Box 23)
  KG11365.678
- Photometric Observations, 1873; phaedra0680 (Box 23)
  KG11365.679
- Photometric Observations, 1873; phaedra0681 (Box 23)
  KG11365.680
- Photometric Observations, 1874; phaedra0682 (Box 23)
  KG11365.681
- Photometric Observations, 1874; phaedra0683 (Box 23)
  KG11365.682
- Photometric Observations, 1874/1875; phaedra0684 (Box 23)
  KG11365.683
- Experiments with Photometer, 1872; phaedra0685 (Box 23)
  KG11365.684
- Eta Centauri Spectral Study, 1911; phaedra0686 (Box 23)
  KG11365.685
  Leah B. Allen
- Clusters - spectrophotmetric tracings, 1930; phaedra0687 (Box 23)
  KG11365.686
  Carol Jane Anger
- Spectrophotometric tracings (Alpha Cyg, Vega), 1930/1936; phaedra0688 (Box 23)
  KG11365.687
- Spectrophotometric tracings (Alpha Cyg, Vega), 1930/1936; phaedra0689 (Box 23)
  KG11365.688
- Eta Per, NGC 663 - spectrophotmetric tracings, phaedra0690 (Box 24)
  KG11365.689
- Clusters - spectrophotmetric tracings, 1932; phaedra0691 (Box 24)
  KG11365.690
- Clusters - spectrophotmetric tracings, 1934; phaedra0692 (Box 24)
  KG11365.691
- Miscellaneous; Variables, 1918/1919; phaedra0693 (Box 24)
  KG11365.692
  Mary D. Applegate
- Variables, Map of the Sky, 1918/1919; phaedra0694 (Box 24)
  KG11365.693
- Map of the Sky, Sequences for Orion Nebula, 1919; phaedra0695 (Box 24)
  KG11365.694
- Asteroids and Novae, 1919/1920; phaedra0696 (Box 24)
  KG11365.695
- Novae and Variables, 1920/1921; phaedra0697 (Box 24)
  KG11365.696
- Map of the Sky, 1920/1921; phaedra0698 (Box 24)
  KG11365.697
- Daily Journal [13-inch - Peru], 1889/1890; phaedra0699 (Box 24)
  KG11365.698
- Double Stars; Planets (13-inch - Peru), 1894/1896; phaedra0700 (Box 24)
  KG11365.699
  25
- Miscellaneous; Variables, 1917/1919; phaedra0701 (Box 24)
  KG11365.700
  Dorothy W. Block
- Spectrum Work, 1917/1919; phaedra0702 (Box 24)
  KG11365.701
- Omicron Ceti, Nova Aql 3, 1917/1919; phaedra0703 (Box 24)
  KG11365.702
- Variables, 1918/1919; phaedra0704 (Box 24)
  KG11365.703
- Asteroids, 1918/1919; phaedra0705 (Box 24)
  KG11365.704
- Variables, 1919; phaedra0706 (Box 24)
  KG11365.705
- Variable Stars and Meteors, 1903; phaedra0707 (Box 24)
  KG11365.706
  Frederick E. Brasch
- Variable Stars, 1896/1898; phaedra0708 (Box 24)
  KG11365.707
  Sarah E. Breslin
- Variable Stars, 1898; phaedra0709 (Box 24)
  KG11365.708
- Variable Stars, 1898; phaedra0710 (Box 25)
  KG11365.709
- Variable Stars, 1899; phaedra0711 (Box 25)
  KG11365.710
- Variable Stars, 1901/1902; phaedra0712 (Box 25)
  KG11365.711
- Variable Stars, 1902; phaedra0713 (Box 25)
  KG11365.712
- Variable Stars, 1902/1903; phaedra0714 (Box 25)
  KG11365.713
- Variable Stars, 1903; phaedra0715 (Box 25)
  KG11365.714
- Variable Stars, 1903; phaedra0716 (Box 25)
  KG11365.715
- Variable Stars, 1903; phaedra0717 (Box 25)
  KG11365.716
  10
- Variable Stars, 1903; phaedra0718 (Box 25)
  KG11365.717
  11
- Variable Stars, 1903/1904; phaedra0719 (Box 25)
  KG11365.718
  12
- Variable Stars, 1904; phaedra0720 (Box 25)
  KG11365.719
  13
- Variable Stars, 1904; phaedra0721 (Box 25)
  KG11365.720
  14
- Variable Stars, 1904; phaedra0722 (Box 25)
  KG11365.721
  15
- Variable Stars, 1904; phaedra0723 (Box 25)
  KG11365.722
  16
- Variable Stars, 1904; phaedra0724 (Box 25)
  KG11365.723
  17
- Variable Stars, 1904/1905; phaedra0725 (Box 25)
  KG11365.724
  18
- Variable Stars, 1905; phaedra0726 (Box 25)
  KG11365.725
  19
- Variable Stars, 1905; phaedra0727 (Box 25)
  KG11365.726
  20
- Variable Stars, 1905/1906; phaedra0728 (Box 25)
  KG11365.727
  21
- Variable Stars, 1906; phaedra0729 (Box 25)
  KG11365.728
  22
- Variable Stars, 1906; phaedra0730 (Box 26)
  KG11365.729
  23
- Variable Stars, 1906; phaedra0731 (Box 26)
  KG11365.730
  24
- Variable Stars, 1906; phaedra0732 (Box 26)
  KG11365.731
- Variable Stars, 1906; phaedra0733 (Box 26)
  KG11365.732
  26
- Variable Stars, 1907; phaedra0734 (Box 26)
  KG11365.733
  27
- Variable Stars, 1907; phaedra0735 (Box 26)
  KG11365.734
  28
- Variable Stars, 1907; phaedra0736 (Box 26)
  KG11365.735
  29
- Variable Stars, 1907/1908; phaedra0737 (Box 26)
  KG11365.736
  30
- Variable Stars, 1908; phaedra0738 (Box 26)
  KG11365.737
  [31]
- Variable Stars, 1908; phaedra0739 (Box 26)
  KG11365.738
  32
- Variable Stars, 1909; phaedra0740 (Box 26)
  KG11365.739
  33
- Variable Stars, 1909/1910; phaedra0741 (Box 26)
  KG11365.740
  34
- Variable Stars, 1910/1911; phaedra0742 (Box 26)
  KG11365.741
  35
- Magnitude Estimates, 1903; phaedra0743 (Box 26)
  KG11365.742
  [4]
- Comparison Stars for Variables, 1922; phaedra0744 (Box 26)
  KG11365.743
  L.A. Brigham
- Variable Stars, 1919; phaedra0745 (Box 26)
  KG11365.744
  Grace R. Brooks
- Variable Stars, 1901/1902; phaedra0746 (Box 26)
  KG11365.745
- Variable Stars, 1902/1903; phaedra0747 (Box 26)
  KG11365.746
- Variable Stars, 1903; phaedra0748 (Box 26)
  KG11365.747
- Variable Stars, 1903/1904; phaedra0749 (Box 26)
  KG11365.748
- Variable Stars, 1904; phaedra0750 (Box 27)
  KG11365.749
- Variable Stars, 1904/1905; phaedra0751 (Box 27)
  KG11365.750
- Variable Stars, 1905/1907; phaedra0752 (Box 27)
  KG11365.751
- Variable Stars, 1907/1908; phaedra0753 (Box 27)
  KG11365.752
- Variable Stars, 1908/1909; phaedra0754 (Box 27)
  KG11365.753
- Variable Stars, 1909/1911; phaedra0755 (Box 27)
  KG11365.754
- Observations with Photographs X on 5-inch, 1903/1906; phaedra0756 (Box 27)
  KG11365.755
- Observations with Photographs X on 5-inch, 1903/1905; phaedra0757 (Box 27)
  KG11365.756
- Observations with Photographs X on 5-inch, 1905; phaedra0758 (Box 27)
  KG11365.757
- Observations with Photographs X on 5-inch, 1906/1907; phaedra0759 (Box 27)
  KG11365.758
- Photometric Observations, 1915; phaedra0760 (Box 27)
  KG11365.759
- 6-inch (west) Equatorial, 1917/1924; phaedra0761 (Box 27)
  KG11365.760
- Memoranda on Variable Stars, 1904/1905; phaedra0762 (Box 27)
  KG11365.761
- 8-inch Polar Telescope, 1908/1909; phaedra0763 (Box 27)
  KG11365.762
- 8-inch Polar Telescope, 1909/1911; phaedra0764 (Box 27)
  KG11365.763
- Variable Star Observations, 1911/1912; phaedra0765 (Box 27)
  KG11365.764
- Variable Star Observations, 1912/1914; phaedra0766 (Box 27)
  KG11365.765
- S I 8 17, 1911/1912; phaedra0767 (Box 27)
  KG11365.766
- Photometric Records, 1913/1915; phaedra0768 (Box 27)
  KG11365.767
- Variable Star Observations, 1914/1915; phaedra0769 (Box 28)
  KG11365.768
- Log Book - Arequipa Station of HCO, 1915; phaedra0770 (Box 28)
  KG11365.769
- P #17, 1913; phaedra0771 (Box 28)
  KG11365.770
- Pyrheliometer 17 Observation, 1914; phaedra0772 (Box 28)
  KG11365.771
- Estimate of Work (Arequipa), 1911; phaedra0773 (Box 28)
  KG11365.772
- Long Period Southern Variables, 1910; phaedra0774 (Box 28)
  KG11365.773
- Variables, 1907/1909; phaedra0775 (Box 28)
  KG11365.774
  E.S. Manson, H.E. Blackett, K.L.
- Long Period Southern Variables, 1904/1908; phaedra0776 (Box 28)
  KG11365.775
- Long Period Southern Variables, 1918; phaedra0777 (Box 28)
  KG11365.776
- Nova Aquilae No. 3, 1918; phaedra0778 (Box 28)
  KG11365.777
- [Untitled], phaedra0779 (Box 28)
  KG11365.778
  Missing. See also KG11366.875
- Variable Star Observations, 1900/1901; phaedra0780 (Box 28)
  KG11365.779
  [I?]
- Visual observations, 1901/1902; phaedra0781 (Box 28)
  KG11365.780
- Visual observations, 1902/1903; phaedra0782 (Box 28)
  KG11365.781
- Visual observations, 1903/1904; phaedra0783 (Box 28)
  KG11365.782
- Visual observations, 1904; phaedra0784 (Box 28)
  KG11365.783
- Visual observations, 1904/1905; phaedra0785 (Box 28)
  KG11365.784
- Visual observations, 1905/1906; phaedra0786 (Box 28)
  KG11365.785
- Visual observations, 1906/1907; phaedra0787 (Box 28)
  KG11365.786
  X
- Visual observations, 1907/1909; phaedra0788 (Box 28)
  KG11365.787
  XI
- Notes for Reading, 1911/1939; phaedra0789 (Box 28)
  KG11365.788
  101
- Guest Book, 1912/1935; phaedra0790 (Box 28)
  KG11365.789
- Variable Stars, Longitude Determination, 1862/1882; phaedra0791 (Box 29)
  KG11365.790
  Seth C. Chandler
- Variable Stars, Longitude Determination, phaedra0792 (Box 29)
  KG11365.791
  Stored under KG11366.1080
- W. Virginis I, 1916; phaedra0793 (Box 29)
  KG11365.792
  Clarence A. Chant
- Lambda of spectra lines in red region of stars, 1926/1927; phaedra0794 (Box 29)
  KG11365.793
  C.T. Chase
- Spectra of Novae, 1926; phaedra0795 (Box 29)
  KG11365.794
  PD 1
  Paul Daidovich
- [Measurements], 1926; phaedra0796 (Box 29)
  KG11365.795
  PD 2
- Journal - Latitude And Longitude Work, 1896; phaedra0797 (Box 29)
  KG11365.796
  [72]
- Radiometric Book I, 1937/1938; phaedra0798 (Box 29)
  KG11365.797
- Radiometry II, 1939/1940; phaedra0799 (Box 29)
  KG11365.798
  E.M. Berson
- Radiometry Program Book I, 1936/1938; phaedra0800 (Box 29)
  KG11365.799
- Galvanometry Book I, 1937/1938; phaedra0801 (Box 29)
  KG11365.800
- Variable Stars, 1890/1892; phaedra0802 (Box 29)
  KG11365.801
  Williamina P. Fleming
- Variable Stars, 1892/1894; phaedra0803 (Box 29)
  KG11365.802
- Variable Stars; Spectra, 1892/1894; phaedra0804 (Box 29)
  KG11365.803
- Variable Stars, 1893/1898; phaedra0805 (Box 29)
  KG11365.804
- Variable Stars, 1894/1895; phaedra0806 (Box 29)
  KG11365.805
- Variable Stars; Spectra, 1895/1899; phaedra0807 (Box 29)
  KG11365.806
- Variable Stars, 1895/1896; phaedra0808 (Box 29)
  KG11365.807
- Variable Stars, 1896; phaedra0809 (Box 29)
  KG11365.808
- Variable Stars, 1896/1897; phaedra0810 (Box 29)
  KG11365.809
- Variable Stars, 1897/1898; phaedra0811 (Box 30)
  KG11365.810
- Variable Stars, 1897/1902; phaedra0812 (Box 30)
  KG11365.811
- Variable Stars, 1898/1903; phaedra0813 (Box 30)
  KG11365.812
- Variable Stars, 1898/1905; phaedra0814 (Box 30)
  KG11365.813
- Variable Stars, 1899/1905; phaedra0815 (Box 30)
  KG11365.814
- Variable Stars; Computations of Spectra, 1903/1907; phaedra0816 (Box 30)
  KG11365.815
- Variable Stars; Computations of Spectra, 1903/1910; phaedra0817 (Box 30)
  KG11365.816
- Variable Stars; Photometer, 1905/1908; phaedra0818 (Box 30)
  KG11365.817
- Novae, Comets, Spectra, 1906/1911; phaedra0819 (Box 30)
  KG11365.818
- Spectral Classification; Miscellaneous Observations, 1908/1911; phaedra0820 (Box 30)
  KG11365.819
- Ledger of LPV's 000339-095659, phaedra0821 (Box 30)
  KG11365.820
- Ledger of LPV's 100661-185905, phaedra0822 (Box 30)
  KG11365.821
- Ledger of LPV's 190048-235939, phaedra0823 (Box 30)
  KG11365.822
- Clusters and Faint Stars, 1904/1911; phaedra0824 (Box 30)
  KG11365.823
- Nova Persei Reductions, 1902; phaedra0825 (Box 30)
  KG11365.824
- Variable Stars, phaedra0826 (Box 30)
  KG11365.825
- Measurements of Bright Line Spectra, 1890; phaedra0827 (Box 30)
  KG11365.826
  Missing 11/1991 (?)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, phaedra0828 (Box 30)
  KG11365.827
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1886/1887; phaedra0829 (Box 30)
  KG11365.828
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1886; phaedra0830 (Box 30)
  KG11365.829
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1886; phaedra0831 (Box 31)
  KG11365.830
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1886/1887; phaedra0832 (Box 31)
  KG11365.831
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, phaedra0833 (Box 31)
  KG11365.832
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1886/1887; phaedra0834 (Box 31)
  KG11365.833
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1886/1887; phaedra0835 (Box 31)
  KG11365.834
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; phaedra0836 (Box 31)
  KG11365.835
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; phaedra0837 (Box 31)
  KG11365.836
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; phaedra0838 (Box 31)
  KG11365.837
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, phaedra0839 (Box 31)
  KG11365.838
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; phaedra0840 (Box 31)
  KG11365.839
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; phaedra0841 (Box 31)
  KG11365.840
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; phaedra0842 (Box 31)
  KG11365.841
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887/1888; phaedra0843 (Box 31)
  KG11365.842
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; phaedra0844 (Box 31)
  KG11365.843
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887/1889; phaedra0845 (Box 31)
  KG11365.844
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, phaedra0846 (Box 31)
  KG11365.845
- Catalog of E. Stars, phaedra0847 (Box 31)
  KG11365.846
- Description of Spectra, 1887/1888; phaedra0848 (Box 31)
  KG11365.847
- Description of Spectra, 1887/1889; phaedra0849 (Box 31)
  KG11365.848
- Catalog of E. Stars, 1882/1924; phaedra0850 (Box 32)
  Inferred
  KG11365.849
  1882phae.proj..850F
- Catalog of E. Stars, 1882/1924; phaedra0851 (Box 32)
  KG11365.850
  1882phae.proj..851F
- Discordant Spectra; Remarks on Rejected Measures, 1882/1924; phaedra0852 (Box 32)
  KG11365.851
  1882phae.proj..852F
- G Standard Stars on Spectrum Plates, 1882/1924; phaedra0853 (Box 32)
  KG11365.852
  1882phae.proj..853F
- E Standard Stars on Spectrum Plates, 1882/1924; phaedra0854 (Box 32)
  KG11365.853
  1882phae.proj..854F
- Description of Spectra, 1888-02-28/1888-06-04; phaedra0855 (Box 32)
  KG11365.854
  1888phae.proj..855F
- G Standard Stars on Spectrum Plates, 1882/1924; phaedra0856 (Box 32)
  KG11365.855
  31
  1882phae.proj..856F
- Description of Spectra, 1888-06-04/1890-04-25; phaedra0857 (Box 32)
  KG11365.856
  1888phae.proj..857F
- C Standard Stars on Spectrum Plates, 1882/1924; phaedra0858 (Box 32)
  KG11365.857
  1882phae.proj..858F
- Catalog of I Plates, 1882/1924; phaedra0859 (Box 32)
  KG11365.858
  1882phae.proj..859F
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1888-09-11/1890-03-11; phaedra0860 (Box 32)
  KG11365.859
  1888phae.proj..860F
- F and G Discordant Spectra, 1882/1924; phaedra0861 (Box 32)
  KG11365.860
  36
  1882phae.proj..861F
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1889-05-01/1889-05-16; phaedra0862 (Box 32)
  KG11365.861
  39
  1889phae.proj..862F
- Catalog of Plates Classes N, H, L; Peruvian Plates, 1889-09-07; phaedra0863 (Box 32)
  KG11365.862
  40
  1889phae.proj..863F
- Catalog of Plates Classes C, D; Peruvian Plates, 1882/1924; phaedra0864 (Box 32)
  KG11365.863
  41
  1882phae.proj..864F
- Objects of Interest on Southern Plates, 1882/1924; phaedra0865 (Box 32)
  KG11365.864
  42
  1882phae.proj..865F
- Objects of Interest on Spectrum Plates, 1890-09-03; phaedra0866 (Box 32)
  KG11365.865
  45
  1890phae.proj..866F
- Objects of Interest on Southern Spectrum Plates, 1898-01-18/1907-12-07; phaedra0867 (Box 32)
  KG11365.866
  97
  1898phae.proj..867F
- Miscellaneous (Ecl, Solar, Etc), 1890-02-05/1891-11-25; phaedra0868 (Box 32)
  KG11365.867
  49
  1890phae.proj..868F
- Discussion of Draper Catalog, 1882/1924; phaedra0869 (Box 32)
  KG11365.868
  50
  1882phae.proj..869F
- Measurement of Spectrum Plates for Southern Draper Catalogue, 1889-09-27/1892-11-20; phaedra0870 (Box 33)
  KG11365.869
  51
  1889phae.proj..870F
- Description of Spectrum Measures for Southern Draper Catalogue, 1890-09-26/1893-05-03; phaedra0871 (Box 33)
  KG11365.870
  [52]
  1890phae.proj..871F
- Discussion of Draper Catalog, 1882/1924; phaedra0872 (Box 33)
  KG11365.871
  53
  1882phae.proj..872F
- Discussion of Draper Catalog, 1882/1924; phaedra0873 (Box 33)
  KG11365.872
  56
  1882phae.proj..873F
- Catalog of Chart Plates (I - 8-inch), 1882/1924; phaedra0874 (Box 33)
  KG11365.873
  57
  1882phae.proj..874F
- Catalog of Chart Plates (I - 8-inch), 1882/1924; phaedra0875 (Box 33)
  KG11365.874
  58
  1882phae.proj..875F
- Catalog of Chart Plates (B in Peru), 1882/1924; phaedra0876 (Box 33)
  KG11365.875
  59
  1882phae.proj..876F
- Measurments of Spectrum Plates, Southern Draper Catalogue, 1892-11-22/1892-12-05; phaedra0877 (Box 33)
  KG11365.876
  61
  1892phae.proj..877F
- Measures of Spectral Plates (South Draper Catalog), 1892-12-11/1893-01-31; phaedra0878 (Box 33)
  KG11365.877
  62
  1892phae.proj..878F
- Measures of Spectrum Plates of Southern Draper Catalogue, 1893-01-31/1893-05-17; phaedra0879 (Box 33)
  KG11365.878
  63
  1893phae.proj..879F
- Measures of Spectrum Plates, Southern Draper Catalogue, 1893-05-20/1893-06-05; phaedra0880 (Box 33)
  KG11365.879
  64
  1893phae.proj..880F
- Measures of Spectrum Plates, Southern Draper Catalogue, 1893-06-05/1893-06-25; phaedra0881 (Box 33)
  KG11365.880
  65
  1893phae.proj..881F
- Measures of Spectrum Plates, Southern Draper Catalogue, 1893-06-27/1893-07-28; phaedra0882 (Box 33)
  KG11365.881
  67
  1893phae.proj..882F
- Measures of Spectrum Plates, Southern Draper Catalogue, 1893-07-28/1893-11-08; phaedra0883 (Box 33)
  KG11365.882
  68
  1893phae.proj..883F
- Measures of Spectrum Plates, Southern Draper Catalogue, 1893-11-08/1894-06-15; phaedra0884 (Box 33)
  KG11365.883
  69
  1893phae.proj..884F
- Measures of Spectrum Plates, Southern Draper Catalogue, 1894-06-20/1903-06-20; phaedra0885 (Box 33)
  KG11365.884
  70
  1894phae.proj..885F
- Description of Spectra Measures Southern Draper Catalogue, 1893-06-01/1894-06-13; phaedra0886 (Box 33)
  KG11365.885
  1893phae.proj..886F
- Draper Catalogue Spectra Class C, 1900; phaedra0887 (Box 33)
  KG11365.886
  1900phae.proj..887F
- Description of Spectra Measures Southern Draper Catalogue, 1894-06-20/1904-07-18; phaedra0888 (Box 33)
  KG11365.887
  1894phae.proj..888F
- Spectra to be confirmed in Catalogue of III Type Stars, 1882/1924; phaedra0889 (Box 33)
  KG11365.888
  1882phae.proj..889F
- Spectra to be confirmed in Catalogue of III Stars, 1882/1924; phaedra0890 (Box 34)
  KG11365.889
  1882phae.proj..890F
- [Notes on Double Stars and Stellar Parallax], 1893; phaedra0891 (Box 34)
  KG11365.890
  1893phae.proj..891F
- Spectra to be confirmed in Catalogue of III Stars, 1882/1924; phaedra0892 (Box 34)
  KG11365.891
  1882phae.proj..892F
- Constraints in South Draper Catalog, 1889; phaedra0893 (Box 34)
  KG11365.892
  Williamina P. Fleming, Jennie T. Rugg
  1889phae.proj..893F
- Reduction of Plates having less than 4 Standard Stars, 1882/1924; phaedra0894 (Box 34)
  KG11365.893
  Associated names:
  Edith F. Gill, Harriet I. Stevens, Amy J. McKay, Mabel C. Stevens, Mabel A. Gill, Florence Cushman, Louisa D. Wells, Evelyn F. Leland, Antonia C. Maury
  1882phae.proj..894F
- Notes on Draper Catalog; Accounts of Share-Holders of the Camera, 1892-05-01; phaedra0895 (Box 34)
  KG11365.894
  [15]
  1892phae.proj..895F
- Measures of Spectrum Plates (South Draper Catalog), 1903-06-24/1904-06-06; phaedra0896 (Box 34)
  KG11365.895
  81
  1903phae.proj..896F
- Measures of Spectrum Plates (South Draper Catalog), 1903-07-23/1903-09-21; phaedra0897 (Box 34)
  KG11365.896
  82
  1903phae.proj..897F
- Measures of Spectrum Plates (South Draper Catalog), 1903-10-30/1904-07-18; phaedra0898 (Box 34)
  KG11365.897
  83
  1903phae.proj..898F
- Objects of Interest - Bruce Spectrum Plates, 1896-12-28/1916-10; phaedra0899 (Box 34)
  KG11365.898
  96
  Williamina P. Fleming, Annie Jump Cannon
  1896phae.proj..899F
- Objects of Interest on northern spectrum plates, 1898-09-23/1911-03-07; phaedra0900 (Box 34)
  KG11365.899
  98
  1898phae.proj..900F
  See KG11355.866 for volume 97
- Objects of Interest - South Bache Plates, 1907-12-07/1911-04-26; phaedra0901 (Box 34)
  KG11365.900
  99
  1907phae.proj..901F
- Variables and Halley's Comet, 1909-12-08/1910-07-06; phaedra0902 (Box 34)
  KG11365.901
  L.S. Flint, L.P.P.
  1909phae.proj..902F
- Catalogue of the Mean Colors of 2149 Southern Stars, 1910; phaedra0903 (Box 34)
  KG11365.902
  William Sadler Franks
  1910phae.proj..903F
- Variables, 1926/1929; phaedra0904 (Box 34)
  KG11365.903
  Boris Petrovich Gerasimovich
  1926phae.proj..904G
- Variables, 1912/1929; phaedra0905 (Box 34)
  KG11365.904
  1912phae.proj..905G
- Variables, 1900/1920; phaedra0906 (Box 34)
  KG11365.905
  1900phae.proj..906G
- Variables, 1899/1927; phaedra0907 (Box 34)
  KG11365.906
  1899phae.proj..907G
- Spectrophotometry of B + O Stars, 1926/1929; phaedra0908 (Box 34)
  KG11365.907
  1926phae.proj..908G
- Variables, 1899/1919; phaedra0909 (Box 34)
  KG11365.908
  1899phae.proj..909G
- Color Indices of Long Period Variables, phaedra0910 (Box 35)
  KG11365.909
- Spectrophotometry of B and Wolf-Rayet Stars, phaedra0911 (Box 35)
  KG11365.910
- Variable Stars, 1900/1927; phaedra0912 (Box 35)
  KG11365.911
- B Star Observations, 1902; phaedra0913 (Box 35)
  KG11365.912
  Maude E. Harriman
- MC Plates taken for Standard magnitude, 1908; phaedra0914 (Box 35)
  KG11365.913
- Measurement of Variable Stars, 1908; phaedra0915 (Box 35)
  KG11365.914
  Margaret Harwood
- Measurement widths of A + B stars, 1922; phaedra0916 (Box 35)
  KG11365.915
  Marian A. Hawes
- Assorted Plate Measurements, 1912/1918; phaedra0917 (Box 35)
  KG11365.916
- 5-inch Equatorial, 1918; phaedra0918 (Box 35)
  KG11365.917
- Variable Stars, 1904/1906; phaedra0919 (Box 35)
  KG11365.918
  Anson S. Leard, Guy Hill
- Variable Star Observations, 1889/1916; phaedra0920 (Box 35)
  KG11365.919
  E.H.
- Color correction for telescope objectives, 1878; phaedra0921 (Box 35)
  KG11365.920
- Assorted Plate Measurements, phaedra0922 (Box 35)
  KG11365.921
  L. Hofrager
- Assorted Plate Measurements, 1928/1930; phaedra0923 (Box 35)
  KG11365.922
- Measurements of Plates, Stars, etc., 1895/1898; phaedra0924 (Box 35)
  KG11365.923
  Edward S. King
- Reductions of Measures, 1899; phaedra0925 (Box 35)
  KG11365.924
- Notes: Photographic Instruments, 1904/1924; phaedra0926 (Box 35)
  KG11365.925
- Measurements: Distances, Altitudes, Plates, 1901/1902; phaedra0927 (Box 35)
  KG11365.926
- Assorted Plate Measurements, 1902; phaedra0928 (Box 35)
  KG11365.927
- Color Distance measurements, 1920-11-04/1927-08-29; phaedra0929 (Box 36)
  KG11365.928
  1920phae.proj..929K
  Transit of Mercury, May 7 1924
- Schilt Photometry, 1927/1928; phaedra0930 (Box 36)
  KG11365.929
  1927phae.proj..930K
- Photographic measurement of light, 1897; phaedra0931 (Box 36)
  KG11365.930
- Computation Book No. 2, 1916; phaedra0932 (Box 36)
  KG11365.931
  1916phae.proj..932K
- Photogrpahic Magnitudes, Misc, 1914/1918; phaedra0933 (Box 36)
  KG11365.932
  Henrietta S. Leavitt
- Variables; Observations, 1902/1903; phaedra0934 (Box 36)
  KG11365.933
  1902phae.proj..934L
- Examination of Plates, 1903; phaedra0935 (Box 36)
  KG11365.934
- Variables, 1903; phaedra0936 (Box 36)
  KG11365.935
- Phoebe, 1904; phaedra0937 (Box 36)
  KG11365.936
  1904phae.proj..937L
- Circumpolar variables, 1895/1896; phaedra0938 (Box 36)
  KG11365.937
- Variable Star Observations, 1896-01-29/1896-03-20; phaedra0939 (Box 36)
  KG11365.938
  Contributor: Genevieve F. Matthews
  Genevieve F. Matthews
- Variable Star Observations, 1896-03-20/1896-05-19; phaedra0940 (Box 36)
  KG11365.939
- Variable Star Observations, 1896-05-19/1902-11-21; phaedra0941 (Box 36)
  KG11365.940
- Variable Star Observations, 1902-11-21/1915-11-08; phaedra0942 (Box 36)
  KG11365.941
- Circumpolar variables, 1902-12-12/1904-01-27; phaedra0943 (Box 36)
  KG11365.942
- Variable Star Observations, 1904-01-27/1904-04-07; phaedra0944 (Box 36)
  KG11365.943
- Miscellaneous Observations, 1904-09-26/1910-08-15; phaedra0945 (Box 36)
  KG11365.944
- Miscellaneous Observations, 1905-02-15/1917-03-29; phaedra0946 (Box 36)
  KG11365.945
- Discovery of New Variables, 1907-02-21/1915-02-09; phaedra0947 (Box 36)
  KG11365.946
- Comparison Stars, 1906-10-16/1921-07-21; phaedra0948 (Box 36)
  KG11365.947